{
    "subject": "resource/Artem_Yarchuk",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Yaroslavl",
    "human_readable": "Artem Yarchuk was born in Yaroslavl.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8634999990463257,
            "question": "Where was Artem Yarchuk born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7752329111099243,
            "question": "What year was Artem Yarchuk born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5997545719146729,
            "question": "In what city did Artem Yarchuk grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5634230375289917,
            "question": "What is Artem Yarchuk known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4439643919467926,
            "question": "Is Artem Yarchuk Russian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.429360032081604,
            "question": "What is Artem Yarchuk's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40045809745788574,
            "question": "Does Artem Yarchuk have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37254467606544495,
            "question": "Has Artem Yarchuk traveled to other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35046276450157166,
            "question": "Where does Artem Yarchuk live now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23608577251434326,
            "question": "What are some of Artem Yarchuk's hobbies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Artem Yarchuk was born in Yaroslavl.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5690_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Artem Yarchuk live now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5690_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Artem Yarchuk traveled to other countries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5690_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Artem Yarchuk have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5690_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5690_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document states that \"Place of Birth: Yaroslavl\" for Artem Yarchuk, which supports the statement that Artem Yarchuk was born in Yaroslavl."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}